Register of the Bonner Frank Fellers Papers, 1904-1997
Hoover Institution Archives
Bonner Frank Fellers papers
1904-1997
70031
Fellers, Bonner Frank, 1896-1973
59 manuscript boxes, 1 oversize box (24 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives
Speeches and writings, studies, reports, correspondence, memoranda, orders, printed matter, and photographs, relating to American propaganda and military activities in the Pacific Theater during World War II, the occupation of Japan, and postwar conservative political organizations in the United States, especially the Citizens Foreign Aid Committee. Described in two groups, first the original accession, then for an addition to the collection in 2003.
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1970, with additional increments in 1976 and 2003.
Chronology
1896 February 7 Born, Ridge Farm, Illinois
1918 B.S., United States Military Academy, West Point
1918 November 1 United States Army (advanced through the grades to Brigadier General, December 1942)
1920 Graduated, Coast and Artillery School
1935 Graduated, Command and General Staff School, Fort Leavenworth, Kansas
1935-1938 Member, General Douglas MacArthur's staff in the Philippines (liaison between MacArthur and Philippine President Quezon)
1940-1942 Military observer with British forces in Africa
1943-1946 Member, General Douglas MacArthur's staff (Hollandia Operation) Military secretary and head of psychological warfare drive against Japanese combat troops
1946 January-August Secretary General, Allied Council for Japan
1946 November 30 Retired from active duty
1947-1952 Assistant to the Chairman of the Republican National Committee
1952 Author, Wings for Peace: A Primer for a New Defense
1959-1969 Chairman, Citizens Foreign Aid Committee
1973 October 7 Died
Scope and Content of Collection
Acquired in 1970, the Bonner Fellers papers relate to American propaganda and military operations in the Pacific Theater during World War II, the occupation of Japan, and postwar conservative political organizations in the United States, especially the Citizens Foreign Aid Committee. The papers consist of speeches and writings, studies, reports, correspondence, memoranda, military orders, and printed matter (boxes 1-16).
Acquired in 2003, the increment to the Bonner Frank Fellers papers in the Hoover Institution Archives (boxes 17-60) substantially increases the volume of the collection. The incremental materials span the lifetime of Fellers, ranging from his numerous military postings to his subsequent civilian career as a political lobbyist and opinion maker.
The Military Career File in the increment contains correspondence and reports pertaining to various assignments carried out by Fellers before and during World War II, including his experiences in the Philippines and Egypt, and later as military secretary to General Douglas MacArthur. This series also contains studies done by Fellers in the field of psychological warfare, especially in relation to the American war effort against the Japanese. There are also records concerning the postwar American occupation of Japan, during which Fellers served in an administrative role.
The extensive Speeches and Writings series includes numerous articles and speeches from the late 1940s through the 1960s, when Fellers wrote and spoke as a conservative and strongly anti-communist critic of American foreign policy during the Cold War. This series also records the public views of Fellers on military strategy, especially the role of air power in modern warfare, and in favor of a dramatic reduction in American foreign aid programs. The manuscript of Fellers' only published book, Wings for Peace, is part of the series. Several of his recorded speeches can be found in the Sound Recordings series of the increment.
There is a substantial Correspondence series in the increment, including exchanges of letters between Fellers and Robert A. Taft, for whom Fellers served as an unofficial adviser and speechwriter. The speeches that Fellers wrote for Taft are also part of the increment. In addition to a significant Subject File, there is a separate Psychological Warfare File that consists of correspondence, writings, and other materials relating to a proposed campaign of propaganda directed at the population of the Soviet Union, a project advocated by Fellers in the 1950s.
Arrangement
The original collection and 1976 increment (boxes 1-16) are arranged into nine series: Writings, Military Files, United States Army Psychological Warfare Branch Files, Miscellany, Correspondence I, Subject File I, Speeches and Writings I, Printed Matter, and an additional incremental series accessioned in 1976.
The Incremental Materials of 2003 (boxes 17-60) are arranged into fifteen series: Biographical File, Correspondence II, Speeches and Writings II, Reports, Speeches and Statements Written for Others, Notebooks, Military Career File, Civilian Career File, Psychological Warfare File, Fellers Family File, Albums, Subject File II, Speeches and Writings by Others, Photographs, Sound Recordings, and Oversize Materials.
A Declassified records series, added in 2011, is arranged chronologically by the date the records were released by Hoover.
Allied Forces. Supreme Headquarters. Psychological Warfare Division.; Citizens Foreign Aid Committee.; Taxpayers Committee to End Foreign Aid.; United States. Army--Officers.; Economic assistance, American.; Philippines--History--Japanese occupation, 1942-1945.; Philippines.; Propaganda, American.; Psychological warfare.; United States--Armed Forces.; United States--Economic conditions.; United States--Foreign relations.; World War, 1939-1945--Philippines.; World War, 1939-1945--Propaganda.; World War, 1939-1945--Psychological aspects.; World War, 1939-1945.
- Writings, 1934-1958. (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents note
  Articles, reports, and studies by Bonner Fellers, arranged alphabetically by title
  - "Answer to Japan,", 1944. (Folder 1: 1)
    Printed copy
  - "Hirohito's Struggle to Surrender,", undated. (Folder 1: 2)
    Typescript
  - "The Psychology of the Japanese Soldier," Fort Leavenworth, Kansas, 1934-1935. (Folder 1: 3)
    Typescript and printed copy
  - "Survival," series of seven articles, Standard-Times, New Bedford, Massachusetts, 1958 July 7-13. (Folder 1: 4)
    Clippings
- Military Files, 1943-1945. (Box 1-3)
  Intelligence reports, memoranda, correspondence, and reports issued by various sections of the United States Army, arranged alphabetically by issuing agency
  - General. "Report on Activities of the Far Eastern Liaison Office for the Period June 1942 to September 1945,", 1945 October 1 (Folder 1: 5)
  - United States. Army. Intelligence reports, 1943 (Folder 1: 6)
  - United States. Army. General Headquarters. South West Pacific Area. Allied Translator and Interpreter Section. "Antagonism between Officers and Men in the Japanese Army," Research Report No. 122, 1945 April 19 (Folder 1: 7)
  - United States. Army. Forces, Pacific
    - General. Circulars, correspondence, memoranda, orders, 1945 (Folder 1: 8)
    - Commander-in-Chief. Leaflet File No. 2, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 2: 1)
    - General Headquarters. Operational instructions
      - 1944 (Folder 2: 2)
      - 1945 (Folder 2: 3)
    - Office of the Assistant Chief of Staff, G-2. Translator and Interpreter Service. Documents Submitted to the Supreme Commander for the Allied Forces by the Japanese Mission to Negotiate Surrender, Manila, 1945 August 19 (Folder 2: 4)
  - United States. Army. Forces, South West Pacific Area. Military Intelligence Section. General Staff. Report on the Destruction of Manila and Japanese Atrocities, 1945 February (Folder 2: 5-6)
  - United States. Army. Forces, Western Pacific. Replacement Command. "American and Allied Personnel Recovered From Japanese Prisons," Manila, Philippine Islands, 1945 November 11 (Box-folder 3: 1)
  - United States. Department of War. Adjutant General's Office. "Publicity in Connection With Escaped, Liberated, or Repatriated Prisoners of War, to Include Evaders of Capture in Enemy or Enemy-Occupied Territory and Internees in Neutral Countries (Recovered Personnel),", 1945 October 4 (Folder 3: 2)
- United States Army Psychological Warfare Branch, 1944-1945. (Box 3-4)
  Correspondence, memoranda, broadcast transcripts, and reports
  - Correspondence and memoranda, 1944-1945, primarily between Brigadier General Fellers and Lieutenant Colonel Woodall Greene. (Folder 3: 3)
    Also included are reports, leaflets, clippings, and other material
  - Memorandum from Brigadier General Fellers to the Commander-in-Chief, regarding American-Japanese relations and the status of the Japanese Emperor, 1945. (Folder 3: 4)
    Also included is a memorandum entitled "Basic Military Plan for Psychological Warfare in the Southwest Pacific Area," 1944, issued by the Planning Group of the Office of Strategic Services
  - United States. Army. Forces, Pacific. Commander-in-Chief. Psychological Warfare Branch. Planning, 1944-1945 (Folder 3: 5-6)
  - United States. Army. Headquarters 5th Army. Psychological Warfare Branch. "Functions of the 5th Army Combat Propaganda Team,", 1944 (Folder 3: 7)
  - United States. Army. Forces, Pacific. Commander-in-Chief. Psychological Warfare Branch. Files, 1944-1945 (Folder 3: 8)
  - Correspondence and memoranda, 1944-1945, primarily between Brigadier General Fellers and Lieutenant Colonel Woodall Greene (Box-folder 4: 1-2)
  - United States. Army. South West Pacific Area. Office of the Military Secretary. Psychological Warfare Branch. Collation Section. Report No. 7, "Psychological Warfare: Reactions and Developments,", 1945 March 10 (Folder 4: 3)
  - United States. Army. South West Pacific Area. Office of the Military Secretary. Psychological Warfare Branch. "Basic Military Plan for Psychological Warfare against Japan,", 1945 April 12 (Folder 4: 4)
  - Broadcast transcript from the headquarters of General MacArthur, entitled "The Philippine Hour,", 1944 September 2 (Folder 4: 5)
  - Various broadcast transcripts from the United States military, 1945, including several by Rear Admiral Zacharias, United States Navy, undated. (Folder 4: 6)
    Also included is correspondence and memoranda, 1944-1945
  - "Psychological Warfare News Coverage in the Philippines,", undated (Folder 4: 7)
  - United States. Army. Forces, Pacific. General Headquarters, Commander-in-Chief. "Report on Psychological Warfare against Japan, South West Pacific Area 1944-1945,", 1946 (Folder 4: 8)
  - United States. Army. General Headquarters. South West Pacific Area. Office of Military Secretary. "Weekly Military Plan for Psychological Warfare,", 1945 June 16 (Folder 4: 9)
  - United States. Army. South West Pacific Area. "Psychological Warfare - It's Role in the Philippines,", undated. (Folder 4: 10)
- Miscellany, 1967-1973. (Box 4)
  Reports, studies, newsletters, leaflets, and obituary
  - "Typical Japanese Atrocities during the Liberation of the Philippines,", undated (Folder 4: 11)
  - "The Nightmare of Lieutenant Ichi, or Juan Posong Gives Ichi the Midnight Jitters,", undated (Folder 4: 12)
  - Leaflets produced by the enemy, undated (Folder 4: 13)
  - Taxpayers Committee to End Foreign Aid (formerly, Citizens Foreign Aid Committee). Newsletters, reports, and statements, 1967-1971 (Folder 4: 14)
  - United States. Congress. Congressional Record. Proceedings and debates of the 93rd Congress, 1st Session, Volume 119, No. 168, Washington, D.C., 1973 November 5. (Folder 4: 15)
    "General Bonner Fellers in Memoriam" by William G. Bray
  - Miscellaneous propaganda posters, undated (Folder 4: 16)
- Correspondence I, 1943-1970. (Box 5)
  Arranged alphabetically by name of correspondent
  - Brophy, Frank Cullen, 1971 (Folder 5: 1)
  - Conklin, Arthur S., 1943. (Folder 5: 2)
  - Davison, L. A., 1968 (Folder 5: 3)
  - De Ganahl, Frank, 1968 (Folder 5: 4)
  - Dennis, W. C., 1943 (Folder 5: 5)
  - Derevyanko, K., 1946 (Folder 5: 6)
  - Donovan, W. J., 1943 (Folder 5: 7)
  - Eichelberger, Robert, 1946 (Folder 5: 8)
  - Giffin, Sid F., 1943 (Folder 5: 9)
  - Harrison, Thomas P., 1959 (Folder 5: 10)
  - Leetch, Mrs. William D., 1968 (Folder 5: 11)
  - Lodge, Cabot, 1943 (Folder 5: 12)
  - Miller, Elizabeth H., 1968 (Folder 5: 13)
  - Murphy, Frank, 1943 (Folder 5: 14)
  - Pew, J. Howard, 1968-1970 (Folder 5: 15)
  - Reese, Carroll, 1943 (Folder 5: 16)
  - Scott, C. L., 1943 (Folder 5: 17)
  - Wiley, John C., 1943 (Folder 5: 18)
- Subject File I, 1934-1972. (Box 5-15)
  Correspondence, memoranda, reports, minutes of meetings, lists, charts, leaflets, notes, printed matter, and clippings, arranged roughly alphabetically
  - Allied Air Forces. South West Pacific Area. Headquarters. Intelligence Summaries, Serial Nos. 283-285, 1945 August (Folder 5: 19)
  - Alumni bills, Philadelphia College of Textiles and Science, 1966-1967 (Folder 5: 20)
  - American Institute Counselors, Incorporated, Investment Bulletins, 1965-1972 (Folder 5: 21)
  - American Institute for Economic Research
    - Economic Education Bulletins and Research Reports, 1963-1972 (Folder 5: 22-25)
    - Research Reports, 1963-1972 (Box-folder 6: 1-4)
  - American Security Council, "Washington Reports,", 1968 (Folder 6: 5)
  - "An Attempt to Estimate the Situation,", 1943 April 23 (Folder 6: 6)
  - "An Attempt to State Our American Problem for 1943,", 1943 May 24 (Folder 6: 7)
  - Broadcast to Japan by Carl W. Ackerman, Manila, 1945 April 27. (Folder 6: 8)
    Transcript
  - "Burma Operation,", undated (Folder 6: 9)
  - Citizens Foreign Aid Committee
    - General, 1959-1967 (Folder 6: 10)
    - Braden, Spruille. Statement before House Appropriations Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, 1959 June 24 (Folder 6: 11)
    - "The Case Against Foreign Aid - A Fourth Report,", 1960 (Folder 6: 12)
    - Clay Committee statements, 1963 (Folder 6: 13)
    - Conference schedule, 1961 September (Folder 6: 14)
    - Congressional statements
      - 1959 (Folder 6: 15)
      - 1960 (Folder 6: 16)
      - 1960 (Box-folder 7: 1)
      - 1961 (Folder 7: 2-3)
      - 1962 (Folder 7: 4-5)
      - 1963 (Folder 7: 6-7)
      - 1964 (Folder 7: 8)
      - 1965 (Box-folder 8: 1-2)
      - 1966 (Folder 8: 3-4)
    - Correspondence
      - Blake, Robert, 1967 (Folder 8: 5)
      - Davison, L. A., 1968 (Folder 8: 6)
      - Dirksen, Everett M., 1959 (Folder 8: 7)
      - Dockman, Robert, 1968 (Folder 8: 8)
      - Fleet, Reuben H., 1966 (Folder 8: 9)
      - Gilbert, Robert A., 1968 (Folder 8: 10)
      - Hayden, Carl, 1959 (Folder 8: 11)
      - Hoerner, Richard N., 1967 (Folder 8: 12)
      - Long, Russell B., 1959 (Folder 8: 13)
      - Nye, Gerald P., 1968 (Folder 8: 14)
      - Oakes, John C., 1959 (Folder 8: 15)
      - Tittman, E. M., 1964 (Folder 8: 16)
      - University of California, Los Angeles, 1969 (Folder 8: 17)
      - University of California, Santa Barbara, 1970 (Folder 8: 18)
      - University of Michigan, School of Library Science, 1970 (Folder 8: 19)
      - Van Vliet, Charles T., 1959 (Folder 8: 20)
      - Young, Milton R., 1959 (Folder 8: 21)
    - Events
      - 1960 (Folder 8: 22-23)
      - 1961 (Folder 8: 24)
    - Extracts from comments supplied by the Department of State, Department of Treasury, Department of Defense, and International Cooperation Administration criticizing "Foreign and You" with a rebuttal, undated (Box-folder 9: 1)
    - "Facts on Foreign Aid"
      - 1960 May-August (Folder 9: 2)
      - 1961 January-September (Folder 9: 3)
      - 1962 January-October (Folder 9: 4)
      - 1963 January-December (Folder 9: 5)
      - 1964 January-October (Folder 9: 6)
      - 1965 January-September (Folder 9: 7)
      - 1966 February-October (Folder 9: 8-9)
      - 1967 January-September (Folder 9: 10)
    - Fellers, Bonner
      - "Our Foreign Aid Cost,", undated (Folder 9: 11)
      - Statement before the House Foreign Affairs Committee, 1967 May 8 (Folder 9: 12)
      - Statement before the Senate Committee on Appropriations, 1967 November 15 (Folder 9: 13)
    - "Foreign Aid - A Message to President John F. Kennedy, A Fifth Report,", 1961 January 20 (Folder 9: 14)
    - "Foreign Aid and You - A First Report,", 1959 (Folder 9: 15)
    - Foreign Assistance Act of 1966, hearings before the Committee on Foreign Affairs, House of Representatives, 1966 April 28 (Folder 9: 16)
    - Foreign Assistance Act of 1967, hearings before the Committee on Foreign Affairs, House of Representatives, 1967 May 8-11 (Folder 9: 17)
    - Groseclose, Elgin
      - Statement before the Committee on Foreign Affairs, House of Representatives, 1967 May 8 (Folder 9: 18)
      - Statement before the Senate Committee on Appropriations, 1967 November 15 (Folder 9: 19)
    - Groseclose, Williams and Associates, "Financial Consequences of Overseas Military Expenditures and Foreign Assistance Program," report to the Citzens Foreign Aid Committee, 1960 February 1 (Folder 9: 20)
    - Harnischfeger, Walter
      - General, 1968-1970 (Folder 9: 21)
      - Address before the 47th annual meeting of the Washington, D.C. Chamber of Commerce, 1959 April 28 (Folder 9: 22)
      - Congressional statements, 1959 (Folder 9: 23)
      - Press release statement, 1959 February 8 (Box-folder 10: 1)
      - Statement before the Senate Appropriations Committee, 1967 November 16 (Folder 10: 2)
    - Heinsohn, A. G., Jr., statement before the House Appropriations Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, 1959 June 14 (Folder 10: 3)
    - Jones, Mark M., president of National Economic Council, Incorporated, statement before the Senate Committee on Appropriations, 1967 November 15 (Folder 10: 4)
    - Lloyd, Lewis E., "Aid and the Dollar Crisis," statement before the House Appropriations Committee on Foreign Operations, 1963 August 14 (Folder 10: 5)
    - Lory, Milton, statement before the House Foreign Affairs Committee, 1867 May 8 (Folder 10: 6)
    - Manion, Dean Clarence, statement before the Senate Committee on Appropriations, 1959 August 20 (Folder 10: 7)
    - Metropolitan Club luncheon, New York City, 1963 January 9 (Folder 10: 8)
    - Murray, Mrs. Robert, statement before the House Appropriations Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, 1959 June 24 (Folder 10: 9)
    - Net foreign aid funds requested for the first seven months of 1967 (Folder 10: 10)
    - New foreign aid funds for fiscal year 1968 (Folder 10: 11)
    - Palyi, Melchior, extract from the statement before the House Appropriations Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, 1959 June 24 (Folder 10: 12)
    - Passman, Otto E., "Socialism or Americanism," address before members of the medical profession, Monroe, Louisiana, 1967 April 15 (Folder 10: 13)
    - Projects completed and material prepared and distributed, 1960 April 1 - June 30 (Folder 10: 14)
    - Tansill, Charles Callau, statement before the Senate Committee on Appropriations, 1959 August 20 (Folder 10: 15)
  - Clark, Fred G., "The Socialist Sixteenth - A National Cancer," address before the Eastern Airlines, Incorporated, annual staff banquet, Miami Beach, Florida, undated (Folder 10: 16)
  - Congressional candidates list, 1968 (Folder 10: 17)
  - Economists National Committee on Monetary Policy, 1965-1969 (Folder 10: 18)
  - "Eleventh Broadcast to the Japanese People," by Captain Zacharias, United States Navy, undated (Folder 10: 19)
  - "Estimate of the Situation with Especial Reference to the Middle East,", 1943 March 12 (Folder 10: 20)
  - Hoover, Herbert, notes from conversations with, 1943 (Folder 10: 21)
  - Institute for Monetary Research, Incorporated, 1971 (Folder 10: 22)
  - Itinerary for Captain Bonner Fellers, 1937 August 28 (Folder 10: 23)
  - Japan, a report
    - 1934 (Folder 10: 24)
    - 1935 (Folder 10: 25)
  - "Japan - It's People, It's History, It's Land, It's Work," reprint, Encyclopedia Britannica, undated (Folder 10: 26)
  - Japan's advances during the period 1941 December 7 to 1942 May 6. (Folder 10: 27)
    Map
  - Japanese Army Division, Imperial Headquarters, list of personnel of Army forces according to areas and classes, 1945 August 31 (Folder 10: 28)
  - Japanese atrocities in the Philippine Islands
    - General
      - 1945
        - February (Folder 10: 29)
        - February-March (Folder 10: 30-31)
        - February-March (Box-folder 11: 1)
        - March-April (Folder 11: 2)
    - Affidavit by Dr. Walter K. Frankel, 1945 February 12 (Folder 11: 3)
  - "Japanese Land Operations (From Japanese Sources), December 8, 1941 to June 8, 1942," Campaign Study No. 3, 1942 November 18, Military Intelligence, United States War Department (Folder 11: 4)
  - Japanese reaction to United States psychological warfare, report, undated (Folder 11: 5)
  - Maps, 1937-1945 (Folder 11: 6)
  - "Notes Recorded on Indoctrination Course in Psychological Warfare Given by Officers of the Far Eastern Liaison Office (Allied Organization),", undated (Folder 11: 7)
  - "Operational Highlights of the 33rd Infantry Division,", 1945 May 15 (Folder 11: 8)
  - Passman, Otto E., "To the American Taxpayer,", 1971 July (Folder 11: 9)
  - Petersen, Howard C., "Needed: A New Foreign Aid Policy,", 1957 (Folder 11: 10)
  - Pew, J. Howard, "Remarks by J. Howard Pew at the William Penn Award Dinner,", 1970 May 21 (Folder 11: 11)
  - Philippine Islands
    - Civil affairs, 1941-1945 (Folder 11: 12-13)
    - Military manpower, undated (Folder 11: 14)
  - "Psychological Warfare with the 1st Cavalry Division,", undated (Box-folder 12: 1)
  - Supreme Commander for the Allied Powers (SCAP). Office of the Military Secretary. Memorandum for the Supreme Commander Allied Powers, 1945 September 10 (Folder 12: 2)
  - Taxpayers Committee to End Foreign Aid
    - General, 1968-1972 (Folder 12: 3-4)
    - Correspondence
      - American Institute for Economic Research, 1970 (Folder 12: 5)
      - Battin, James F., 1968 (Folder 12: 6)
      - Bergsten, C. Fred, 1969 (Folder 12: 7)
      - Braun, Victor F., 1968 (Folder 12: 8)
      - Brixius, Robert C., 1968 (Folder 12: 9)
      - Brophy, Frank Cullen
        - 1968 (Folder 12: 10)
        - 1971 (Folder 12: 11)
      - Buck, J. F., 1968 (Folder 12: 12)
      - Campbell, Albert M., 1968 (Folder 12: 13)
      - Chartener, William H., 1969 (Folder 12: 14)
      - Christensen, L. N., 1968 (Folder 12: 15)
      - Crawford, Frederick C., 1968 (Folder 12: 16)
      - Davison, L. A., 1969 (Folder 12: 17)
      - 18 Day, Henry L., 1968 (Folder 12: 18)
      - Day, James M., 1968 (Folder 12: 19)
      - Dee, John A., 1968 (Folder 12: 20)
      - Del Valle, P. A., 1968 (Folder 12: 21)
      - Densford, Charles F., 1968 (Folder 12: 22)
      - Dockson, Robert R., 1968 (Folder 12: 23)
      - Export-Import Bank of the United States, 1972 (Folder 12: 24)
      - Fleming, Malcolm N., 1968 (Folder 12: 25)
      - Garvey, William W., 1968 (Folder 12: 26)
      - Grabar, Lee, 1968 (Folder 12: 27)
      - Grede, William J., 1969 (Folder 12: 28)
      - Harnischfeger, Walter, 1971 (Folder 12: 29)
      - Hartke, Vance, 1968 (Folder 12: 30)
      - Hoerner, R. N., 1968 (Folder 12: 31)
      - Hummon, John, 1969 (Folder 12: 32)
      - Jones, Mark M., 1968 (Folder 12: 33)
      - Klein, Herbert G., 1969 (Folder 12: 34)
      - Lawrence, David, 1969-1970 (Folder 12: 35)
      - Loeb, William, 1968-1969 (Folder 12: 36)
      - McCracken, Paul W., 1969 (Folder 12: 37)
      - McGrath, William L., 1968-1969 (Folder 12: 38)
      - Manion, Dean C., 1968-1971 (Folder 12: 39)
      - Martin, William M., 1969 (Folder 12: 40)